<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS type="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<!-- /*******************************************************************************
 * Copyright (c) 2000, 2005 IBM Corporation and others.
 * All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials
 * are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0
 * which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
 * http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html
 * 
 * Contributors:
 *     IBM Corporation - initial API and implementation
 *******************************************************************************/ -->
<contexts>
<context id="sdpd0000">
<description>This dialog box displays the status of the projects that were published. For more detailed information, click <b>Details</b>. A scrollable box appears at the bottom of this dialog box.

</description>
</context>
<context id="sdpd0002">
<description>This dialog box displays the status of the projects that were published. For more detailed information, click <b>Details</b>. A scrollable box appears at the bottom of this dialog box.

</description>
</context>
<context id="sdpd0004">
<description>This dialog box displays the status of the projects that were published. For more detailed information, click <b>Details</b>. A scrollable box appears at the bottom of this dialog box.

</description>
</context>
<context id="sdpd0006">
<description>This dialog box displays the status of the projects that were published. For more detailed information, click <b>Details</b>. A scrollable box appears at the bottom of this dialog box.

</description>
</context>

<context id="sdpi0000">
<description>This change cannot be undone.

</description>
</context>
<context id="sdti0000">
<description>Informational message indicating that server is not responding and that you may want to terminate it by clicking <b>OK</b>.

</description>
</context>
<context id="spge0000">
<description>Use to set the preferences that servers will use for testing projects.

</description>
</context>

<context id="spge0002">
<description>Specifies that all the files should automatically be published to the local server at every <b>seconds</b> intervals, where <b>seconds</b> is the number of seconds you have specified in the control.
</description>
</context>
<context id="spge0006">
<description>Specifies that all the files should automatically be published to the remote server at every <b>seconds</b> intervals, where <b>seconds</b> is the number of seconds you have specified in the control.
</description>
</context>
<context id="spge0012">
<description>Specifies that all the files should automatically be published before starting the server.
</description>
</context>

<context id="spge0014">
<description>Specifies that the server tools can automatically restart the server when it detects that the server must be restarted to handle resource changes in the workspace.
</description>
</context>


<context id="spge0020">
<description>Specifies that the server tools will prompt you before you make a change in a editor that cannot be undone.
</description>
</context>

<context id="spge0022">
<description>The Servers view is displayed on the workbench when there are any activities in the Servers view.
</description>
</context>

<context id="spge0024">
<description>Specifies the preferences for saving the changes in any open server editors before starting the server. Select <b>Never</b> to never save the changes in any open editors before starting the server. Select <b>Prompt</b> to have the server tools prompt you before saving any changes in an open server editor. Select <b>Always</b> to have the server tools automatically save any changes in an open server editor before starting the server.
</description>
</context>

<context id="spge0026">
<description>Select the relative length of time you can wait before ending a server operation.
The default setting is <b>Normal</b>.
<b>Tip</b>:  If you have a fast processing machine, you can try using the <b>Shorter</b> timeout delay option.  If you have a slow processing machine, you can try using the <b>Longer</b> timeout delay option.
</description>
</context>

<context id="spge0028">
<description>This option specifies that each time you start the workbench, it will try to update the status of the server defined in the Servers view with the actual state of the server, such as Started or Stopped.
</description>
</context>

<context id="spge0030">
<description>When switching the server to run in a different mode, for example using the <b>Run As</b> > <b>Run on Server</b>, <b>Profile As</b> > <b>Profile on Server</b>, or <b>Debug As</b> > <b>Debug on Server</b>, specify the next action of the server by selecting one of the following options:

<b>Restart</b> - specifies the workbench to stop and restart the server

<b>Continue</b> - specifies to continue running the server in previous mode and ignore the change request of running in a different server mode

<b>Prompt</b> - specifies the workbench to prompt you for the next server action when you switch the server to run in a different mode
</description>
</context>

<context id="spge0031">
<description>When you finish running the server in debug mode and switch out, for example using the <b>Run As</b> > <b>Run on Server</b> or <b>Profile As</b> > <b>Profile on Server</b> command, specify the next action of the server by selecting one of the following options:

<b>Restart</b> - specifies the workbench to stop and restart the server

<b>Disable breakpoints</b> - specifies to clear all previously set breakpoints from the application and continue running the application in the newly selected server mode

<b>Continue</b> - specifies to continue running the server in debug mode and ignore the change request of running in a different server mode

<b>Prompt</b> - specifies the workbench to prompt you for the next server action when switching the server out of debug mode
</description>
</context>

<context id="spge0032">
<description>When you change the server mode into debug mode, for example using the <b>Debug As</b> > <b>Debug on Server</b> command, specify how to handle the breakpoints currently set in your application by selecting one of the following options:

<b>Always</b> - specifies to enable all the currently set breakpoints in your application and break at them

<b>Never</b> - specifies the workbench to ignore all the breakpoints previously set in your application and continue running the application on the server in debug mode. When the workbench ignores all the breakpoints in your application, the behavior of the server mode is similar to using the <b>Run on Server</b> command. However, because the server is running in debug mode, you have the opportunity to enable or re-enable breakpoints in your application.

<b>Prompt</b> - specifies the workbench will prompt you on how to handle the breakpoints set in your applications
</description>
</context>

<context id="svcp0000">
<description>The Server view allows you to manage servers. This view displays a list of all your servers and the server configurations that are associated with each server. You can use this view to start, start in debug mode, restart, and stop servers.

</description>
</context>
<context id="svcp0002">
<description>
This dialog box prompts different options depending on the status of the server in the Servers view:

<b>Delete unused server configurations</b>: If server configuration files were created in the workspace under a server project, this option becomes available. Select this check box to remove the server configuration files from the workspace. 
<b>Delete running servers</b> This option specifies to delete servers that are still running.  
<b>Stop servers before deleting</b> This option is only available if the Delete running servers option is selected. This option specifies to stop running servers prior to removing them from the Servers view. If this option is cleared and the Delete running servers option is selected, no stop command is issued against the server, and as a result the server is left running after removing the server from the Servers view.

Select the <b>OK</b> button to apply your delete options.
</description>
</context>
<context id="swic0000">
<description>Use to import a server configuration that is located outside of the workspace but is on the same machine.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swic0002">
<description>The name assigned to the server configuration that you want to import.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swic0004">
<description>The name of the server project that will contain the server configuration that you want to import. Select the name from the list of available server projects.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swic0006">
<description>The type of server configuration that will be imported. Select a type from the list of available configuration types.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swic0008">
<description>The location from which you want to import a server configuration. You may either type the fully qualified pathin the <b>Location</b> field if you know it, or click <b>Browse</b> to find it.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swic0010">
<description>The location from which you want to import a server configuration. You may either type the fully qualified path in the <b>Location</b> field if you know it, or click <b>Browse</b> to find it.

</description>
</context>

<context id="swns0000">
<description>This wizard creates a new server and a new server configuration. A server contains information required to point to a specific run-time environment for local or remote testing, or for deployment to an application server. A server configuration contains information required to set up and deploy to a server.

</description>
</context>

<context id="swns0006">
<description>The type of environment that you want to use for this server. A list of available server types is shown. For more details on each of the supported server types, select a type from the list and read the description that appears in the <b>Description</b> area of this wizard page.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swsc0000">
<description>If a resource can run on several server clients, this dialog box will display them allowing you to select which one will be used.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swsc0002">
<description>If a resource can run on several server clients, this dialog box will display them allowing you to select which one will be used.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swsi0000">
<description>Select a server to launch.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swsi0002">
<description>Select an existing server.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swsi0004">
<description>List of existing servers that can be launched.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swsi0010">
<description>Create a new server to launch.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swsi0012">
<description>List of types of servers that can be launched.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swsi0014">
<description>A preferred server is the server that you want to use when a project has more than one server defined. Click to set the selected server as your preferred server.

</description>
</context>
<context id="swsl0000">
<description>To confirm that you want to launch the selected object, click <b>Finish</b>.

</description>
</context>

<context id="seop0000">
<description>Specify the host name and other server settings.
</description>
</context>

<context id="seop0002">
<description>Specify the name assign to the server.  This name is displayed in the Servers view under the Server column.
</description>
</context>

<context id="seop0004">
<description>Specifies the location where the server configuration files are stored on the workbench.  
For example, if you specified the Configuration path to be <b>/Servers/Tomcat v4.1 Server @ localhost-config</b>, the files are available in the Navigator view, expand the folders: Servers > Tomcat v4.1 Server @ localhost-config.
</description>
</context>

<context id="seop0006">
<description>The fully qualified DNS name or IP address of the host machine where the server is running.
</description>
</context>

<context id="seop0008">
<description>Specifies the name of the installed server runtime environment as defined in the Preferences page (Window > Preferences > Server > Installed Runtimes).
The installed server runtime environment defines the runtime environment of an application server for compiling your application.
To change the installed server runtime enviornment, select the Edit runtime link.
</description>

</context>
<context id="seop0010">
<description>Specify to use the publishing settings as defined in the Preferences page (Windows > Preferences > Server).
</description>
</context>

<context id="seop0012">
<description>Specifies that all the files should automatically be published to the server at every <b>seconds</b> interval, where <b>seconds</b> is the number of seconds you have specified in the <b>Publishing interval</b> control.  The minimum value for the publishing interval is ten seconds.
</description>
</context>

<context id="seop0016">
<description>Specifies the tools should never publish files to the server.
</description>
</context>

<context id="swmm0000">
<description>In the Available projects list, specify the projects that you want to add to the server by clicking the <b>Add</b> button. When you select a project to add to the server, only the projects that are applicable to the type of server will appear. To remove a project from the Configured projects list, click the <b>Remove</b> button.
</description>
</context>
</contexts>